asenna is one of the most feature reach
project management tools on the market
right now but as a WordPress user when
you are looking for smooth clean and
simple project management tool which is
not complex especially WordPress
compatible Flyn wordss totally wins the
game today I'm going to import my Asana
projects to fln boards without losing a
bit of data and also explore the plugin
a little bit so let's get started it
only takes a few steps to import your as
project into flown boards to kick things
off go to EST dashboard and open your
project you will see a drop- down menu
right after the name of your project
open it and Export it in Json
format next go to the boards tab on flu
boards and click on the more icon to
find the import feature select import
from Asana and upload the Json file you
exported then hit start importing and
your projects will be added to fluent
boards without losing any data from ASA
looks cool right fb's UI is clean
userfriendly and uncluttered so you can
navigate through the plugin without any
complexity here you have three different
view modes including the calendar and
Canan view you can smoothly drag and
drop your task between stages also
create new stages for different purposes
adding a new task is even cooler give it
a name and here you are a lot of
features to make your task well detailed
also uncluttered you can assign your
work WordPress users as assign is as
many as you want no limitation at all
set a specific due Deb with time and
priority of your task for the project
also label it with colorful tags need
more you can always create new levels
and edit your existing
ones but the most important thing for
setting a task is the description
because it's always a plus to write down
your task details and necessary
information or attachments in an
organized way so everyone stays on the
right track and you can attach files or
links just inside your task so when
anyone opens the task they'll find them
you can break down your complex and big
task into small subtasks and assign
members to each of them and when a
subtask is completed the assign can mark
them completed also you can transform
your subtask into a task and transform
your task into a subtask plus the
comment section is great for team
communication and adding your
suggestions and notes also you can
always check any kind of changes
happening on your task on the activity
another cool thing you will get in Asana
is the custom field feature if you think
you need more to add to your task this
feature lets you add five types of
fields including checkbox date and
select for instance I have taken the
checkbox
field oh are you a flint CRM user as
well good news for you you can also add
your CRM contacts on your task this
helps your team members to communicate
their needs directly to the client
through automated email sequences or
personalized messaging so you won't have
to go back and forth between your
project team and client so you have your
task ready and if you think you will
frequently need tasks like this one you
can save it as a template that you can
keep editing or create a template from
scratch well this background looks a bit
dull for me let's change it you can see
a lot of icatching wallpapers in three
different categories you can choose one
from them or upload your own pictures
and set it as a
wallpaper just like I did on task you
can add labels and members from this
menu as well plus to stay notified about
your project board you can turn on
notification specify your notification
preferences by toggling on and off and
you can also manage your board members
on the settings you can assign members
roles and give give them specified
access so even in your absence your
trusted members can manage the board but
of course only things that you give
access to and it's time to speak about
our latest inclusion fluent road map as
it comes with fluent wordss Pro you need
nothing exra to have it with its help
you can be on the same page with your
clients and manage any project
fluently not just that if you want
everyone involved in your project to
have the access to the project board
fronted portal can be your friend in
need once you set up the portal you can
give access to your team members clients
or anyone without letting them know
what's going on the back end okay here's
the deal as as pricing plan offers their
starter plan for about $131 yearly but
if you get fluent boards now you have a
great deal because your LTD deal is
going on with 40% discount and you will
get the single side plan for only $149
for a lifetime means lifetime update and
support as well so ultimately we all
have different needs if you are looking
for a project management tool on
WordPress feature it pack simple clean
and dynamic at the same time then fluent
boards is just for you because being
affordable and compatible with WordPress
FL Birds is a solution for every task
for every team so get FL Birds now and
manage your projects with the ultimate
efficiency
[Music]